A Guide to the Papers of the English-Speaking Union, 1952-1987
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the English-Speaking Union, 1952-1987
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
10599-b
This collection consists of 520 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Scope and Content Information
Additional records of the organization include correspondence, activity and financial reports, minutes, membership rosters, printed material on the Union; reports from the Hospitality, Nominating, Program, and Scholarship Committees; and a photograph album.
Contents List
- Annual Activities Reports 1979-1987 (Box 1)
- Board of Directors 1983-1986 (Box 1)
- By-Laws 1967, 1985 (Box 1)
- Dinners and Teas Committee 1983-1986 (Box 1)
- Essay Contest 1983-1984 (Box 1)
- Financial Reports 1983-1987 (Box 1)
- Hospitality Committee 1980-1986 (Box 1)
- Invitations 1984-1987 (Box 1)
- Membership Committee 1979-1987 (Box 1)
- Membership Rosters 1978-1987 (Box 1)
- Minutes 1980-1987 (Box 1)
- Miscellaneous Printed 1984, n.d. (Box 1)
- Nominating Committee 1983-1987 (Box 1)
- Photograph Album of Activities 1986-1987 (Box 2)
- President's Correspondence 1952-1987 (Box 2)
- Program Committee 1983-1986 (Box 2)
- Regional Chairman and National Officers 1983-1986 (Box 2)
- Scholarship Committee 1958-1987 (Box 2)
- Secretary 1982-1986 (Box 2)
- Speakers and Programs 1983-1985 (Box 2)
- Treasurer 1983-1986 (Box 2)